export const sets = [
  {
    title: 'Learn the capitals',
    description: 'Learn the capitals of the world with this set!',
    private: false,
    cards: 10,
    id: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    title: 'Learn Programming Languages',
    description: 'Learn all the programming languages and acronyms!',
    private: false,
    cards: 10,
    id: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    title: 'Learn colors in German',
    description: 'Learn top 10 color names in German!',
    private: true,
    cards: 10,
    id: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
];

export const cardsCapitals = [
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Tokyo located in?',
    answer: 'Japan',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Paris located in?',
    answer: 'France',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Nairobi located in?',
    answer: 'Kenya',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Sydney located in?',
    answer: 'Australia',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Rio de Janeiro located in?',
    answer: 'Brazil',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Cairo located in?',
    answer: 'Egypt',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Moscow located in?',
    answer: 'Russia',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Toronto located in?',
    answer: 'Canada',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Lima located in?',
    answer: 'Peru',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the city of Beijing located in?',
    answer: 'China',
    set: 'rec_ck42n8eorcivm6sm7eag',
  },
];

export const cardsProgramming = [
  {
    question:
      "Which programming language is known for its use in web development and has a popular framework called 'Express.js'?",
    answer: 'JavaScript (Node.js)',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which language is known for its concurrency model and channels?',
    answer: 'Go (or Golang)',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "Which language uses the 'Rails' framework for web development?",
    answer: 'Ruby',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "What does the acronym 'API' stand for?",
    answer: 'Application Programming Interface',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which programming language is often associated with scientific computing, data analysis, and machine learning?',
    answer: 'Python',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "What does the acronym 'SQL' stand for?",
    answer: 'Structured Query Language',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "Which programming language has a mascot named 'Camel'?",
    answer: 'Perl',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "What does the acronym 'IDE' stand for in software development?",
    answer: 'Integrated Development Environment',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which language was primarily developed by Microsoft and is known for its '.NET' framework?",
    answer: 'C#',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
  {
    question: "What does the acronym 'OOP' stand for in programming?",
    answer: 'Object-Oriented Programming',
    set: 'rec_ck44d1lah98vi3sb4oj0',
  },
];

export const cardsFarbenDeutsch = [
  {
    question: 'What is the word for "black" in German?',
    answer: 'schwarz',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "red" in German?',
    answer: 'rot',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the German word for "blue"?',
    answer: 'blau',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "green" in German?',
    answer: 'grün',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you translate "yellow" to German?',
    answer: 'gelb',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you know what the word for "orange" is in German?',
    answer: 'orange',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "brown" in German?',
    answer: 'braun',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the German word for "purple"?',
    answer: 'lila',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'Could you tell me how to say "pink" in German?',
    answer: 'rosa',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
  {
    question: 'And what is the word for "white" in German?',
    answer: 'weiß',
    set: 'rec_cmfv33m68lqgl3jt3im0',
  },
];
